http://www.lichfield.anglican.org/privacy-notice.php

Find a job
HomeAbout UsAbout UsOur Diocesan StaffOur VisionOur VisionMission Projects Discipleship, Vocation And EvangelismShaping For MissionSt Chads Retreat CentresSt Chads Retreat CentresThe Bungalow At DovedaleShallowford HouseDovedale HouseOur OrganisationSearchPeople SearchBishops And ArchdeaconsBishops And ArchdeaconsBishopsBishopsChad 2 Chad Pilgrimage - Lent 2018A New Diocesan Bishop: Rt Revd Dr Michael Ipgrave's 'Season Of Welcome 'Bishop's Lent AppealsAd ClerumsAd ClerumsSafeguarding In The Diocese Of LichfieldLocal Lay Ministry ArrangementsWelcoming And Honouring LGBT+ People In The Diocese Of LichfieldHoly Communion And Reserved SacramentHoly Week And Easter 2020ArchdeaconsArchdeaconsArchdeacons' VisitationsAnnual Parochial Church MeetingsNew Arrangements For PCC Meetings During CoronavirusGuidance On Age Limits For Licensed MinistryDocumentsPhotosPhotosSocially-distanced SeatingNewsOur FaithOur FaithFuneralsChristeningsWeddingsDiocesan Services OnlineDiocesan Services OnlineHoly Week & Easter ResourcesPrayer DiaryComfort And JoyJoin Worship OnlineChad LivingThe Community Of St ChadTwo Saints Way2020 Lent PledgesThy Kingdom ComeThy Kingdom ComeThy Kingdom Come - 2019EventsSafeguardingSafeguardingSafeguarding And Covid-19Safeguarding Training Safeguarding Training Safeguarding Training For The Walsall ArchdeaconrySafeguarding Training For The Lichfield ArchdeaconrySafeguarding Training For The Salop ArchdeaconrySafeguarding Training For The Stoke Upon Trent ArchdeaconrySafeguarding Key ResourcesDBS - Key ResoucesCoronavirus InfoCoronavirus InfoThe Ministry ShiftOnline Worship And ResourcesOnline Worship And ResourcesPrayer At Home And OnlineAt-home Resources For Children's, Youth And Families' MinistryDigital Tools For Online WorshipSpace For Learning
Home > Privacy Notice
This is the Website privacy policy. We also have an overarching privacy policy covering the wider functions of the Diocese relating to data from church officers, clergy and diocesan staff here.
This website privacy policy applies between you, the User of this Website and Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance (LDBF), the owner and provider of this Website. Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance takes the privacy of your information very seriously. This privacy policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us or provided by you in relation to your use of the Website. Please read this privacy policy carefully.
Definitions and interpretation
1. In this privacy policy, the following definitions are used:
Data
collectively all information that you submit to Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance via the Website. This definition incorporates, where applicable, the definitions provided in the Data Protection Act 1998;
Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance,or us
Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance, a company incorporated in England and Wales with registered number Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance (Incorporated) whose registered office is at ST MARYS HOUSE, THE CLOSE, WS13 7LD;
User or you
any third party that accesses the Website and is not either (i) employed by Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance and acting in the course of their employment or (ii) engaged as a consultant or otherwise providing services to Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance and accessing the Website in connection with the provision of such services; and
Website
the website that you are currently using, https://www.lichfield.anglican.org/, and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions.
2. In this privacy policy, unless the context requires a different interpretation:
the singular includes the plural and vice versa;
references to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices are to sub-clauses, clauses, schedules or appendices of this privacy policy;
a reference to a person includes firms, companies, government entities, trusts and partnerships;
"including" is understood to mean "including without limitation";
reference to any statutory provision includes any modification or amendment of it;
the headings and sub-headings do not form part of this privacy policy.
Scope of this privacy policy
3. This privacy policy applies only to the actions of Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance and Users with respect to this Website. It does not extend to any websites that can be accessed from this Website including, but not limited to, any links we may provide to social media websites.
Data collected
4. We may collect the following Data, which includes personal Data, from you:
Name
Date of Birth;
Gender;
Job Title;
Contact Information such as email addresses and telephone numbers;
in each case, in accordance with this privacy policy.
Our use of Data
5. For purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance is the "data controller".
6. We will retain any Data you submit for 12 months.
7. Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to any third party disclosures specifically set out in this policy, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties. This does not include our affiliates and / or other companies within our group.
8. All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. For more details on security see the clause below ( Security).
9. Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Website. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:
internal record keeping;
improvement of our products / services;
Updates on Diocesan events and information concerning the Diocese as a whole;
in each case, in accordance with this privacy policy.
Third party websites and services
10. Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with certain processes necessary for the operation of the Website. The providers of such services do not have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Website.
11. Please note that when data is shared on the website or third-party websites, including social media sites, that the forward sharing of any information is not within our control.
Links to other websites
12. This Website may, from time to time, provide links to other websites. We have no control over such websites and are not responsible for the content of these websites. This privacy policy does not extend to your use of such websites. You are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them.
Changes of business ownership and control
13. Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this privacy policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us.
14. We may also disclose Data to a prospective purchaser of our business or any part of it.
15. In the above instances, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring your privacy is protected.
Controlling use of your Data
16. Wherever you are required to submit Data, you will be given options to restrict our use of that Data. This may include the following:
use of Data for direct marketing purposes; and
sharing Data with third parties.
Functionality of the Website
17. To use all features and functions available on the Website, you may be required to submit certain Data.
Accessing your own Data
18. You have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal Data held by Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance (where such Data is held) on payment of a small fee, which will not exceed £0.
Security
19. Data security is of great importance to Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected via this Website.
20. If password access is required for certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.
21. We endeavour to do our best to protect your personal Data. However, transmission of information over the internet is not entirely secure and is done at your own risk. We cannot ensure the security of your Data transmitted to the Website.
General
22. You may not transfer any of your rights under this privacy policy to any other person. We may transfer our rights under this privacy policy where we reasonably believe your rights will not be affected.
23. If any court or competent authority finds that any provision of this privacy policy (or part of any provision) is invalid, illegal or unenforceable, that provision or part-provision will, to the extent required, be deemed to be deleted, and the validity and enforceability of the other provisions of this privacy policy will not be affected.
24. Unless otherwise agreed, no delay, act or omission by a party in exercising any right or remedy will be deemed a waiver of that, or any other, right or remedy.
25. This Agreement will be governed by and interpreted according to the law of England and Wales. All disputes arising under the Agreement will be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English and Welsh courts.
Changes to this privacy policy
26. Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance reserves the right to change this privacy policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Website and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the privacy policy on your first use of the Website following the alterations.
You may contact Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance by email at info@lichfield.anglican.org.
Can't find what you are looking for? Click here for help
Find staff email addresses through their departments -  check here
Lichfield Diocesan Board of Finance,
St Mary’s House, The Close, Lichfield WS13 7LD
01543 306030
Cookies Policy | Privacy Notice
This website is powered by Church Edit| Privacy Notice
